{"data":[{"question":"You _____ (have) enough to eat?\nYes, I _____ (have) plenty, thank you.","a":"have you had\/have had","b":"have you haved\/have haved","c":"has you haved\/has haved","d":"has you had\/have had","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Have\/has + S + past participle...?\n- I have had...","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"You _____ (dive) from the ten-metre board yet?\nNo, I _____","a":"has you dived\/haven't","b":"have you dived\/haven't","c":"have you dived\/hasn't","d":"has you dived\/hasn't","answer":"2","explain":"- The question form: Have\/ has + S + past participle...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"Someone _____ (wind) the clock?\nYes, Tom _____.","a":"has someone wound\/has","b":"have someone wound\/has","c":"have someone wound\/have","d":"has someone wound\/have","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Have\/ has + S + past participle...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"Mary _____ (water) the tomatoes?\nYes, I think she _____.","a":"have Mary watered\/has","b":"has Mary watered\/has","c":"has Mary watered\/have","d":"have Mary watered\/have","answer":"2","explain":"- The question form: Have\/has + S + past participle...?","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"The post _____ (come)?\nYes, it _____.","a":"has the post come\/has","b":"have the post come\/has","c":"has the post come\/have","d":"have the post come\/have","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Have\/has + S + past participle...?\n- Come -> come (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"How long you _____ (know) Mr Pitt?\nI _____ (know) him for ten years.","a":"have you knowed\/have knowed","b":"have you known\/has known","c":"have you known\/have known","d":"have you knowed\/has knowed","answer":"3","explain":"- We use the present perfect to say how long for an activity that happened in the past, and continues now (for ten years)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"Would you like some coffee?\nI just _____ (make) some.","a":"have just made","b":"have just maked","c":"has just made","d":"has just maked","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the present perfect for recent happenings with just","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"You _____ (see) my watch anywhere?\nNo, I'm afraid I _____.","a":"have you seen\/haven't","b":"have you seed\/haven't","c":"have you seen\/hasn't","d":"has you seen\/haven't","answer":"1","explain":"- The question form: Have\/has + S + past participle...?\n- See -> seen (irregular verb)","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"There aren't any buses because the drivers _____ (go) on strike.","a":"has gone","b":"have gone","c":"have goed","d":"has goed","answer":"2","explain":"- We use the present perfect when there is a connection with now, an action in the past and has a result now.","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"5"},{"question":"I _____ (live) here for ten years.","a":"have lived","b":"has lived","answer":"1","explain":"- We use the present perfect to say how long for an activity that happened in the past, continues now\n- I has lived....","category":"2","subcategorylv1":"5","subcategorylv2":"2","type":"7"}]}